<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Systematizing Systematization of Knowledge</title>
    <link>https://oaklandsok.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Systematizing Systematization of Knowledge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://oaklandsok.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Systematizing Systematization of Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://oaklandsok.github.io/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oaklandsok.github.io/main/</guid>
      <description>Systematizing Systematization of Knowledge Since 2010, the IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy (&#34;Oakland&#34;conference) has included papers on Systematization of Knowledge(SoK). This paper track grew out of discussions at the NSF/IARPA/NSA Workshop on theScience of Security held at the Claremont Resort in November2008. This site collects all the Oakland SoK papers, as well as SoK papers in IEEE European Symposium on Security and Privacy (EuroS&amp;amp;P).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systematizing Systematization of Knowledge - Authors</title>
      <link>https://oaklandsok.github.io/authors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oaklandsok.github.io/authors/</guid>
      <description>SoK Authors  AbdelRahman Abdou
SoK: Delegation and Revocation, the Missing Links in the Web&amp;rsquo;s Chain of Trust (EuroS&amp;amp;P 2020)
Hadi Abdullah
SoK: The Faults in our ASRs: An Overview of Attacks against Automatic Speech Recognition and Speaker Identification Systems (Oakland 2021)
Yasemin Acar
SoK: Lessons Learned From Android Security Research For Appified Software Platforms (Oakland 2016)
Sadia Afroz
SoK: Towards Grounding Censorship Circumvention in Empiricism (Oakland 2016)
Mustaque Ahamad</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systematizing Systematization of Knowledge - Other Conferences</title>
      <link>https://oaklandsok.github.io/others/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oaklandsok.github.io/others/</guid>
      <description>Other Conferences Since IEEE Security and Privacy started the SoK papers in 2010, several other venues have also include SoK papers. (Please let me know if you know of any others that are not listed here.)
Security Conferences ACM Workshop on Artificial Intelligence and Security (started in 2012, continuing)
IEEE European Symposium on Security and Privacy (EuroOakland) (since first edition in 2016)
Privacy Enhancing Technologies Symposium (PETS) (since 2016)
Symposium on Usable Privacy and Security (SOUPS) (started in 2019)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>